{
    "questionBank": [
        {
            "question": "Which of the following creates the correct syntax of an multidimensional array  called page",
            "a": "char[][] = new page[30][100];",
            "b": "char[][] page = new char[30][100];",
            "c": "new char[][] page = char[30][100];",
            "d": "page = new page[30][100]<char>;",
            "correctAnswer": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Is a multidimensional array an array of arrays?",
            "a": "No",
            "b": "I dont know",
            "c": "Yes",
            "d": "I don't know, but with sass",
            "correctAnswer": "c"
        },
        {
            "question": "let's say there exists 'int[][] inputArr' How do you get the height of this multidimensional array?",
            "a": "inputArr.length",
            "b": "inputArr[0].length",
            "c": "inputArr[-1].length",
            "d": "inputArr[0][0].length",
            "correctAnswer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "lets say there exists an multidimensional array 'int[][] inputArr = new int[25][25]'. how do you access the bottom right most element?",
            "a": "inputArr[24][24]",
            "b": "inputArr[0][0]",
            "c": "inputArr[0][24]",
            "d": "inputArr[24][0]",
            "correctAnswer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the super Constructor?",
            "a": " allows you invoke a constructor of the base class within the definition of a derived class constructor",
            "b": "A more safer way to invoke a constructor",
            "c": "Allows you to inherit from multiple constructors",
            "d": "Deez nutz, ha goteeeeem",
            "correctAnswer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of these statements is NOT about inheritance?",
            "a": "it is one of the main techniques of OOP",
            "b": "means that a very general form of a class can be defined and compiled",
            "c": "process by which a new class—known as a derived class—is created from another class, called the base class.",
            "d": "all is correct",
            "correctAnswer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "let's say there exists 'int[][] inputArr' How do you get the width of this multidimensional array?",
            "a": "inputArr.length",
            "b": "inputArr[0].length",
            "c": "inputArr[-1].length",
            "d": "inputArr[0][0].length",
            "correctAnswer": "b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these is the JAVA syntax that allows a class to inherit from another class?",
            "a": ":",
            "b": "inherits",
            "c": "superclass",
            "d": "extends",
            "correctAnswer": "d"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does overriding mean?",
            "a": "The base class method being redefined in the derived class",
            "b": "The derived class method being redefined in the base class",
            "c": "It makes sure the derived class method cannot redefine its method",
            "d": "It makes sure the base class method cannot redefine its method",
            "correctAnswer": "a"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does inheritance NOT do",
            "a": "It reduces code length",
            "b": "It increases cpu performance",
            "c": "It makes your code more readable",
            "d": "Makes pete into an OP programmer",
            "correctAnswer": "b"
        }
    ]
}